<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<startdate><![CDATA[2016-10-01]]></startdate>
		<starttime><![CDATA[08:30:00]]></starttime>
		<enddate><![CDATA[]]></enddate>
		<title><![CDATA[Monday Bike Ride for Intermediate Road Cyclists]]></title>
		<locationinfo><![CDATA[Mon Aug 1\\Home Depot Parking Lot (South End near the HD nursery)\8:30 am]]></locationinfo>
		<description><![CDATA[This is a nobody-gets-left-behind, social ride from Home Depot to Bread.  Weêll meet in the south parking lot at Home Depot (by their nursery); ride the Animas River Trail to E. 32nd St., 32nd to Bread where weêll stop for coffee and pastries.  From Bread, weêll take Florida Rd.-15th St. to Rotary Park where weêll rejoin the Animas Trail and return to Home Depot.   Weêll leave HD promptly at designated start time.  Helmets required. Contact me if you have questions and to be added to an email list so you can be notified of cancellations due to weather, etc.\Ride leader: Helen Root, helen@northandroot.com, 505-320-3441.\Co-leader: Hugh Brown, hugh.m.brown2@gmail.com, 970-403-3089.  ]]></description>
		<difficultyinfo><![CDATA[Moderate\\16 miles roundtrip]]></difficultyinfo>
		<email><![CDATA[helen@northandroot.com]]></email>
	</node>
	<node>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<startdate><![CDATA[2016-10-01]]></startdate>
		<starttime><![CDATA[07:00:00]]></starttime>
		<enddate><![CDATA[]]></enddate>
		<title><![CDATA[Hike to Island & Ice Lakes]]></title>
		<locationinfo><![CDATA[Mon Aug 1\ACP 7:00 am\TC    7:10 am\Purg  7:30 am]]></locationinfo>
		<description><![CDATA[A perennial favorite for the spectacular mountain scenery, beautiful alpine lakes and abundant wild flowers.  The loop includes both Island & Ice Lakes.\Carpool  $6,  Limit 15, Dogs OK\RSVP Norm Stern 385-8554 normstern@frontier.net ]]></description>
		<difficultyinfo><![CDATA[Hard\Moderate\Pace\6.5 miles\2850ê]]></difficultyinfo>
		<email><![CDATA[normstern@frontier.net]]></email>
	</node>
	<node>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<startdate><![CDATA[2016-10-02]]></startdate>
		<starttime><![CDATA[08:00:00]]></starttime>
		<enddate><![CDATA[]]></enddate>
		<title><![CDATA[Little Giant Peak via Little Giant Basin]]></title>
		<locationinfo><![CDATA[Tue Aug 2\ACP 8:00 am\TC 8:10 am\Purg 8:30 am]]></locationinfo>
		<description><![CDATA[Drive up steep jeep road for 3 miles, then hike on trail through Little Giant Basin to ridgeline, continue along ridge to Little Giant Peak (13,416ê). Route includes some off-trail hiking and scrambling. The views are spectacular and wildflowers should be abundant. Moderate pace. Carpool $10, 4WD Lo/HC, Limit 12, Well-behaved dogs and owners OK (dog limit 2).\RSVP Lyle Hancock lylehancock@bresnan.net ]]></description>
		<difficultyinfo><![CDATA[Hard\(moderate pace)\6 miles\2,250ê]]></difficultyinfo>
		<email><![CDATA[lylehancock@bresnan.net]]></email>
	</node>
</data>
